Contact

danielle.nielsen234@gmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/daniellenielsen-bsn-rn-7b02aa145 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Danielle Nielsen, BSN, RN

Assistant Facility Nurse Manager at Americas ER site 001 LLC Sight Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Life Support, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), TNCC, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focus from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

Americas Er Site 001 LLC Sight Assistant Facility Nurse Manager November 2018 - Present (1 year 7 months) Magnolia, TX

Huntsville Memorial Hospital Emergency Room Registered Nurse June 2015 - Present (5 years)

Kingwood Hospital Emergency Room Registered Nurse June 2014 - December 2014 (7 months) Kingwood, Texas

Emergency room nurse

CHI St. Luke's Health Staff RN February 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 7 months) The Woodlands, Texas

Medical surgical nurse at the LakeSide

Health South Rehab Hospital Staff RN February 2012 - February 2013 (1 year 1 month)

Education

Grand Canyon University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2013 - 2015)

Lone Star College
ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2011)